foreign
Market mood check and you know it's
turning out to be a marvelous Monday for
the markets given the fact that you know
we have conquered that 18 600 Mark and
you know the journey from 18 500 to 18
600 took just like half a session on
their belts and you know what's notable
is the fact that Nifty Bank index has
hit a fresh record in fact it was
trading above that 44 400 Mark even and
remember in Friday session we had the
fmcg index also hitting a fresh record
so all in all all the sectors are
participating barring the Pharma uh in
index and the oil and gas index we come
to the greeners and losers in a bit but
you know what's also eating sentiment is
the fact that you know U.S lawmakers
have reached a debt ceiling deal in
principle which of course will be taken
up by the U.S Congress and an approval
is awaited from there but you know the
optimism over that is something that has
spurred Global markets if you look at
Nikki that index is up and at a 33 year
high even though Korean markets are shot
and Shanghai and hansing are muted but
Nikkei is reacting positively and of
course U.S markets are shut tonight on
the back of Memorial Day so the impact
of this news will play out uh tomorrow
when it comes to the U.S markets so I
think uh the voting in the Congress will
happen somewhere on Wednesday so that's
that's one key event that the global
markets will be watching out for for and
you know that's something that the
positive sentiment of course has had a
rub-off effect on the Bulls on the lull
Street and the Bulls have gone berserk
for now so uh good going and you know as
I was mentioning aside of Banks fmcg and
metals are some of the other sectoral
gainers uh a side of Pharma and uh Oil
and Gas Energy all the sectors are
trading in the green if you look at some
of the gainers on the Nifty m m of
course you know brokerages have a very
good view on the stock a positive view
on the stock and that's why the stock is
up nearly four four to five percent yeah
in today's session you have hindalco
inducing Bank ITC another 52-week
another fresh 52 week high on the
counter appearing at around 450 rupees
are there outs HDFC twins also doing
fairly well on the losing end on GC on
the back of poor earnings One Time Hit
yeah and that's something that dragged
the strong down you have Sun Pharma
comments coming in from the management
saying that they expect a single digit
growth going forward and of course
they're you know their offered to
acquire 100 stake in Taro as well that's
kind of weighing down on sentiment uh
aside of that you have DB's labs and HCL
Tech among the top losers uh talking
about Eminem you know just in a bit of
details SUV segment could grow at over
10 that's what the management is saying
and brokerages have upped their target
saying that you know even in tractor
segment even though El Nino concerns are
there there could be sizable market
share games for the company and that is
something that is booting well for the
company let's talk about some of the mid
cap movers in the trade quite a few yeah
so clearly the market is doing well the
mid cap indices are up nearly half half
percent each and if you look at the
gainers right now Mahindra life that is
one stock which is up eight percent I
say lumbar foreign
by September uh you know 2023 which is
in the next three months they'll take up
their stake and gradually they'll be
hiking their steak in order to make it a
fully owned subsidiary uh uh you know
and this is quite important because
they've got the RBA approval with this
regard so this is a positive coming in
foreign
momentum six percent up for that one
bhel uh uh surprise mover in trade today
because the management comment in other
words they're expecting their power
segment to be 50 of the total revenue
then margins to be at uh you know much
higher level from here on I think
because of the power sector demand the
overall the audiobook for bhel should be
moving up is what the street is
expecting gmr infra very weak numbers
and pledge concerns have come in stock
is down 10 City Union Bank seven percent
down Bal Krishna Industries today is
down you know six and a half percent uh
slight recovery after the management is
expecting some margin uptick in fy24 but
yes some weak numbers coming in there
and if you look at the small cap under
the market that is also quite good
colorizer bank that's not the four
percent Sultan is a four percent and
iron Ox wind after uh strong uh you know
management commentary that stock is up
nearly 13 last I mentioned you know
nothing else I also want to talk about
clean science there was a block deal in
the counter somewhere around three and a
half percent stake has exchanged hands
at a price of 14 10 Rupees per share
aside of that what's doing well is NCC
of course on the back of good earnings
you had nuclear soft I think it reported
during marketing Friday right and it's
extending its gain up 20 even another 20
another 20 right uh well these uh when
you talk about earnings IRCTC and adani
transmission will be reporting their
earnings today also this week msci
reject announcement will come in on
Wednesday if I'm not mistaken advani
transmission adani total gas are
expected to exit the standard index and
we can see Hal uh making an increase so
that's one development we will be
watching out for uh side of that GDP
growth GDP data for Q4 and f520 will
also be declared this week I think
Wednesday evening so that's one data
point to watch out for and of course the
developments on the debt ceiling front
when it comes to the US so all these
developments will be closely watched out
for this week and aside of that you know
when you talk about the markets in fine
petrol nothing to complain everybody is
up and about about looking cheerful this
Monday and we will have to see whether
we can just I think we will be able to
give the fact that advanced decline
ratio is pretty strong in favor strongly
in favor of other advances so I mean
that's about it today is the move
doesn't shake us quite a few in trade
losers very few and far between
and of course you know we will be
getting you all the market close action
at 3 30 PM so you can tune in then and
we'll talk about how the markets shut
shop for the day but for now everything
is looking uh Hill and Hearty for the
markets and it's a good buy from me and
nothing thanks a lot for watching very
much
[Music]